Erik Portillo

Front-End Developer

Profile

Experienced developer skilled in HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap, JavaScript, and React. knowledgeable in responsive web design and git version control as well as database creation and e-commerce web apps.

Projects

MyFlix Movie App

- Developed a movie app using the MEAN stack
- Tools used were Angular and Material UI
- View project

Employment History

Web Designer at LiveFit Apparel

January 2021 — Present

- Optimizing website experience by reading user feedback, reviewing website analytics, suggesting improvements, and implementing approved enhancements
- Assisting in content creation and digital advertising
- Uploading products and tracking product ad campaigns

BI Report Developer at JLS Data Services

January 2020 — August 2020

- Designed, built and deployed BI solutions
- Collaborated with teams to integrate systems
- Created visualizations and reports for requested projects

Corporate Trainer at The One Group

April 2016 — December 2019

- Assisted in training staff with new skills and knowledge
- Worked close with CEO, VP and stakeholders
- Planned and implemented an effective training curriculum

Education

Full Stack Development, Career Foundry

October 2020 — May 2021

Completed an eight-month full-stack web development course, I built a Native Chat App, as well as a Full-Stack Project using the MERN stack.

Information Technology, Valencia College

August 2011 — May 2013

Contact

407-432-3075 erikportillo1@gmail.com Portfolio LinkedIn

Skills

HTML/CSS

Wireframing

Prototyping

JavaScript

React

React Native

Data Visualization

Bootstrap

Adobe XD

SQL

Firebase